<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rules>
    <data>
        <game>mastermind</game>
       	<desc>Mastermind is a color-finding single-player game 
in which the player has ten steps to guess which 
colors are hidden in what order.
Gameplay: 
There are four hidden colors at the beginning 
of the game, you have to guess in ten steps, 
with 8 color buttons. After each guess, 
the pins show how successful the colors and 
their order were.
The number of hits that are in it and in the 
right place are indicated in black color. 
And with a white color, that are in it, 
but not in the right place.
You can submit your tip with Submit button 
or you can change it with Back button.
	</desc>
    </data>
    <data>
        <game>2048</game>
        <desc>2048 is played on a 4*4 grid, with numbered
tiles that slide when a player moves them
using W(up), S(down), A(left), D(right) keys.
Every turn, a new tile will randomly appear
in an empty spot on the board with a
value of either 2 or 4. If two tiles
of the same number collide while moving,
they will merge into a tile with the
total value of the two tiles that collided.
The game is won when a tile with a
value of 2048 appears on the board,
hence the name of the game. When the
player has no legal moves the game ends.
        </desc>
    </data>
    <data>
        <game>tictactoe</game>
        <desc>Tic-tac-toe, noughts and crosses, or Xs and Os,
is a paper-and-pencil game for two players, X
and O, who take turns marking the spaces in a 3×3
grid.The player who succeeds in placing three of
their marks in a horizontal, vertical, or diagonal
row is the winner. In this game it is possible
to play against an AI or a chosen opponent of
yours.
        </desc>
    </data>
    <data>
        <game>snake</game>
        <desc>  This game is about a snake which has a liking in
  apples. Your goal is to feed the snake with as
  many apple as possible. Everytime your snake
  eats an apple its stomach gets bigger and
  bigger. Be careful because a long snake is
  harder to control than a smaller snake. You
  must avoid the snake to crash into its own body
  because then your snake gets tangled,
  consequently you can not continue to eat apples
  and the game is over. You should avoid crashing
  into the walls as well because then your snake
  is hurt and your game is over. A snake with a
  big belly is happier than a snake with a small
  belly. Try to be the one who gets its snake
  the longest and happiest.</desc>
    </data>
</rules>